http://www.barcodesolutions.co.uk/privacy-policy/

Home
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Privacy statement We are committed to protecting your privacy. We will only use the information that we collect about you lawfully (in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998) and according to the Which? Web Trader Code of Practice.We collect information about you for 2 reasons: firstly, to process your order and second, to provide you with the best possible service.We will not e-mail you in the future unless you have given us your consent.We will give you the chance to refuse any marketing email from us or from another trader in the future.The type of information we will collect about you includes: your nameaddressphone numberemail addressWe will never collect sensitive information about you without your explicit consent.The information we hold will be accurate and up to date. You can check the information that we hold about you by emailing us. If you find any inaccuracies we will delete or correct it promptly.The personal information which we hold will be held securely in accordance with our internal security policy and the law and the Which? Web Trader Code.If we intend to transfer your information outside the EEA (European Economic Area) we will always obtain your consent first.We may use technology to track the patterns of behaviour of visitors to our site. This can include using a "cookie" which would be stored on your browser. You can usually modify your browser to prevent this happening. The information collected in this way can be used to identify you unless you modify your browser settings.
01482 650596
sales@barcodesolutions.co.uk
help & Info
Account Application
Contact Us
Current Vacancies
Info Links
Privacy Policy
Copyright © 2017 Barcode Solutions (Europe) Ltd, All rights reserved.
eCommerce Designed & Powered by
